be it due to critical illnesses or any
other diseases treatment costs can
severely impact finances but having the
right support can help make your journey
to Better Health seamless introducing
data AIG criti Medicare a comprehensive
policy that provides various specialized
options and coverage for up to 100
critical illnesses Tata AIG criti
Medicare provides lump sum amount with a
sum and short ranging up to rupees two
crores upon the diagnosis of a critical
illness under smart Century Premier plan
or smart half century plan our multi-pay
feature allows you to get claims three
times once under each category so you
get complete financial support and also
provides additional sum in short for
various stages of cancer including early
stage cancer that's not all cancer 360
degree insurance plan provides coverage
for medical expenses for cancer
treatment as well as free and post
hospitalization expenses
Home Care treatment for cancer
chemotherapy and radiotherapy as well as
other Advanced treatments for cancer
Global cover Transportation expenses and
many more here's how the plan works
let's say Mr Kumar is covered under Tata
AIG criti Medicare with smart Century
Premier plan and cancer 360 degree with
a sum in short of rupees 10 lakhs each
as well as Hospital cash along with Tata
AIG criti Medicare which provides rupees
1000 per day for up to 30 days of
hospitalization during that year if Mr
Kumar gets diagnosed with all the three
stages of cancer upon filing a claim
with data AIG he can Avail rupees 2
lakhs for early stage rupees 13 lakhs
for major stage and rupees 5 lakhs for
advanced stage cancer plus up to rupees
10 lakhs for other cancer related
treatments and hospitalization as well
as receive rupees 1000 per day for up to
30 days of hospitalization what's more
oh well Assurance benefit if availed
along with the critical illness plan
also provides lump sum amount to cover
expenses in case of a major or minor
surgery or any other post-operation
procedures and more with Tata AIG critty
Medicare B Leach are ready for more
information visit our website or contact
our advisor